    <!--
    - Database: 'test'
    -->
    <database name="test">
        <!-- Table posts -->
        <table name="posts">
            <column name="id">1</column>
            <column name="user">johndoe</column>
            <column name="title">The Good Place</column>
            <column name="post">Perfect. Just perfect. I appreciate that the series ended at the right time, and I can feel that it served its exact purpose. The whole cast/crew deserves a standing ovation. Every detail of this series is so meaningful, funny, sad, smart, emotional.</column>
            <column name="date">0000-00-00 00:00:00</column>
        </table>
        <table name="posts">
            <column name="id">2</column>
            <column name="user">johndoe</column>
            <column name="title">The Good Place</column>
            <column name="post">The Good Place is a fantastic show that I will forever remember fondly and to anyone reading this I hope you give the show a chance and watch it through.</column>
            <column name="date">0000-00-00 00:00:00</column>
        </table>
        <table name="posts">
            <column name="id">3</column>
            <column name="user">johndoe</column>
            <column name="title">The Good Place</column>
            <column name="post">I love this show. It's a feel good comedy that's lighthearted and will make you laugh while still trying to get some good life lessons across. </column>
            <column name="date">2020-11-20 16:55:25</column>
        </table>
        <table name="posts">
            <column name="id">4</column>
            <column name="user">johndoe</column>
            <column name="title">The Good Place</column>
            <column name="post">After watching the last two final episodes of this series I've changed my rating from 8 to 10. Why? Because I loved the last two episodes - the simple and sweet ending they gave to this awesome show, with no twists whatsoever. Gonna miss this show.</column>
            <column name="date">2020-11-20 16:55:25</column>
        </table>
        <table name="posts">
            <column name="id">5</column>
            <column name="user">johndoe</column>
            <column name="title">The Good Place</column>
            <column name="post">I thought this would be boring, but watched the pilot... then the second episode... then the third... fourth... fifth... sixth... seventh... and came full-stop only because those are the only episodes I could watch now On Demand.</column>
            <column name="date">2020-11-20 16:55:25</column>
        </table>
        <table name="posts">
            <column name="id">6</column>
            <column name="user">johndoe</column>
            <column name="title">The Good Place</column>
            <column name="post">The good place is when a tv show is changing the world for the better.</column>
            <column name="date">2020-11-20 16:55:25</column>
        </table>
        <table name="posts">
            <column name="id">7</column>
            <column name="user">johndoe</column>
            <column name="title">The Good Place</column>
            <column name="post">Honestly, this show is fun. That's the bottom line for it. I have watched the first eight episodes so far, and it's not the funniest or most clever TV I have every watched, but it was fun to view.</column>
            <column name="date">2020-11-20 16:55:25</column>
        </table>
        <table name="posts">
            <column name="id">8</column>
            <column name="user">johndoe</column>
            <column name="title">The Good Place</column>
            <column name="post">One of the most inquisitive and exquisite shows ever made. So deep on so many levels but yet fascinatingly simple. Goodness, beauty, happiness, truth. Simply transcending.</column>
            <column name="date">2020-11-20 16:55:25</column>
        </table>
        <table name="posts">
            <column name="id">9</column>
            <column name="user">johndoe</column>
            <column name="title">The Good Place</column>
            <column name="post">There are very few tv shows/movies that I give 10 stars - and The Good Place is one of them.</column>
            <column name="date">2020-11-20 16:55:25</column>
        </table>
        <table name="posts">
            <column name="id">10</column>
            <column name="user">johndoe</column>
            <column name="title">The Good Place</column>
            <column name="post">I almost didn't watch The Good Place, but I was pleasantly surprised. It is well done and very entertaining. The writers have done a nice job of designing a biting satire on thinking about the afterlife without attacking any real religion in particular.</column>
            <column name="date">2020-11-20 16:55:25</column>
        </table>
        <table name="posts">
            <column name="id">11</column>
            <column name="user">johndoe</column>
            <column name="title">The Good Place</column>
            <column name="post">I've been watching the Good Place since it was first release and now that it's over I can say that it never disappointed.</column>
            <column name="date">2020-11-20 16:55:25</column>
        </table>
        <table name="posts">
            <column name="id">12</column>
            <column name="user">johndoe</column>
            <column name="title">The Good Place</column>
            <column name="post">I wasn't too sure about this series at the start but after getting halfway through I was hooked! The actors all play their role perfectly and the humor is very well constructed. I will be sad to see it end.</column>
            <column name="date">2020-11-20 16:55:25</column>
        </table>
    </database>
